National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 568-698 (Box 15)
  - Docket No. 797. Award No. 811. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Stron. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 798. Award No. 812. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Stewart. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 799. Award No. 813. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Kisner. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Docket No. 800. Award No. 814. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Stewart. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 801. Award No. 815. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Stott. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 802. Award No. 816. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Anderson. Chanute, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. 803. Award No. 817. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Stott. Argentine, Kansas., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 804. Award No. 818. Gulf, Colorado and Santa Fe Railway. Gainesville, Texas. Hatcher., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Docket No. 816. Award No. 819. Atlantic Coast Line. Richmond, Virginia., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 848. Award No. 823. Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railway. Wishram, Washington Terminal., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 857. Award No. 824. Pennsylvania Railroad. BW Redman., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Docket No. 782. Award No. 825. Spokane International Railroad. William Reynolds., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 818. Award No. 826. Union Pacific Railroad Co. Los Angeles Terminal Coach Yard., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 820. Award No. 827. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. H. Roedel., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 821. Award No. 828. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Argentine Yard., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 822. Award No. 829. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Oakland, California., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 823. Award No. 830. Chicago Great Western Railway. R. Jefferson., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 825. Award No. 831. Southern Railway. John Sevier Yard, Knoxville, Tennessee., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Docket No. 829. Award No. 835. Pennsylvania Railroad. William Wooton., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Docket No. 830. Award No. 836. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis. Compton Avenue, St. Louis, Missouri., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Docket No. 831. Award No. 837. The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Docket No. 832. Award No. 838. The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co. Assistant General Yardmasters., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 699-803 (Box 16)
  - Award No. 1157-1182. Docket No. 1144. Chicago and North Western. Escanaba Freight Yard Claims., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1185. Docket No. 1221. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. WT Hildebrandt Discipline., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1186. Docket No. 1222. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. JE Wellington Discipline., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1187. Docket No. 1223. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. McBee Claims., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1188. Docket No. 1224. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Claims for July 21 1951 and Subsequent Claims., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1197. Docket No. 1262. Chicago and North Western. James Kramer., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1198. Docket No. 1266. Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Co. Claim of WB George., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1203. Docket No. 1236. Chicago and North Western., 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 1204. Docket No. 1238. Chicago and North Western Railway. Clinton Briggs., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1205. Docket No. 1240. Erie Railroad Co. Frank Young McMahon. Vacation Pay., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 1206. Docket No. 1245. Chicago Great Western Railway. Vacation Pay for Deceased Yardmaster., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 1183-1208. Docket No. 1235-1261. Chicago and North Western. DF Preadel., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1184. Docket No. 1241. Lehigh Valley Railroad. JW Walton, Jr. Claims., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1212. Docket No. 1267. Louisiana and Arkansas Railway. ED Strange., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1214. Docket No. 1270. Chicago and North Western., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1215. Docket No. 1295. The Washington Terminal. CD Dempsey, OC Nolan., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1221. Docket No. 1247. Chicago and North Western. JH Brazier and CR Richardson., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1073. Docket No. 1089. Union Railroad. Notice to Third Party., 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1228. Docket No. 1188. Chicago and North Western. JH Brazier Claim at Green Bay., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1229. Docket No. 1189. Chicago and North Western. ER Dahl Claim at Waukegan., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1230. Docket No. 1197. Chicago and North Western. EC Decker Claim., 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1231. Docket No. 1196. Chicago and North Western. WW Adams Claim., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1232. Docket No. 1198. Chicago and North Western. JW Hanson Claim., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1233. Docket No. 1200. Chicago and North Western. JH Sarson Claim., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 1234. Docket No. 1199. Chicago and North Western. D. Herlehy Claim., 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 1235. Docket No. 1203. Chicago and North Western. RM Mason Claim., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 1236. Docket No. 1207. Chicago and North Western. LJ Stift Claim for September 12 1956., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 1237. Docket No. 1201. Chicago and North Western. JH Sarson Claim., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 804-923 (Box 17)
  - Docket No. 292. Award No. 304. Long Island Railroad., 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 312. Award No. 309. Pennsylvania Railroad. Detroit. VW Smith., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 308. Award No. 315. Claim of RW Cook., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 314. Award No. 311. George F Neely. Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co., 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 318. Award No. 313. Northern Pacific Railroad. SB Miller. Spokane, Washington., 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 315. Award No. 321. Russell Car Shop. Chesapeake and Ohio., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 317. Award No. 317. PH Buchanan., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Docket No. 315. Award No. 321. Original File. Russell Car Shop., 1931-1946 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 319. Award No. 322. Pennsylvania Railroad. Detroit. VW Smith., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 305. Award No. 314. Southern Railway Case. Knoxville. John Sevier., 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Docket No. 311. Award No. 316. Claim of Fred S. Jones., 1944-1946 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 320. Award No. 327. OLD Hump. Chesapeake and Ohio. Russell, Kentucky., 1941-1946 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 315. Award No. 321. Russell Car Shop. Chesapeake and Ohio., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. Exhibit in Connection with OLD Hump Case. Award No. 327., 1945 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 335. Award No. 336. Hugh Doherty. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Ogden Union Railroad and Depot. Docket No. 371. Award No. 352., 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 371. Award No. 352. JR Morris and JE Newey. Ogden Union Railroad and Depot., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 349. Award No. 354. Edmiston, Powers, Crass. TRRA., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Docket No. 353. Award No. 356. HC Oliver. Pennsylvania., 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 336. Award No. 337. EC Goodale. Southern Pacific Railroad., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 345. Award No. 345. Jacksonville Terminal Co. Withdrawn., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 350. Award No. 349. WG Gretsch. St. Louis-San Francisco Railway., 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 354. Award No. 357. Pennsylvania Railroad. Massillon, Ohio., 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 355. Award No. 358. Pennsylvania Railroad. Peterson, Pennsylvania., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 356. Award No. 359. Pennsylvania Railroad. Vandergrift, Pennsylvania., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Docket No. 357. Award No. 360. Pennsylvania Railroad. New Kensington, Pennsylvania., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Docket No. 358. Award No. 361. Pennsylvania Railroad. Verona, Pennsylvania., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Docket No. 359. Award No. 362. Pennsylvania Railroad. Blairsville, Pennsylvania., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Docket No. 361. Award No. 364. Pennsylvania Railroad. West End, Eastbound Receiving Yard. Pitcairn, Pennsylvania., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad. Metal Yard, Pitcairn, Pennsylvania. Docket No. 362. Award No. 365., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Docket No. 363. Award No. 366. Pennsylvania Railroad. Dock Junction, Erie, Pennsylvania., 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Docket No. 360. Award No. 363. Pennsylvania Railroad. Lima, Ohio., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 924-1028 (Box 18)
  - Public Law Board No. 2046. Cases 1-3., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Public Law Board No. 2055. Award No. 1. Interpretation., 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Public Law Board No. 2037. Case No. 321. Consolidated Rail Corporation., 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Public Law Board No. 2055. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. Hearing date January 25 1978. Referee Sickles. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Public Law Board No. 2060. Louisville and Nashville Railway Co. Yardmaster GW Cunningham., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Withdrawn and settled on property.
  - Public Law Board No. 2059. Baltimore and Ohio No. 13. EL Frey., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Public Law Board No. 2060. Louisville and Nashville No. 18. WN Dixon., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Public Law Board No. 2060. Louisville and Nashville. Case No. 2. MR Clark., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 2061. Chesapeake and Ohio Case No. 48. Eugene Miller., 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Public Law Board No. 2069. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Case No. 85. AJ Mezzatesta., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cost of Living Allowance Documents., 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cost of Living Allowance., 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Public Law Board No. 2145. Baltimore and Ohio Case No. 13. LG Gilley., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Public Law Board No. 2287. Conrail Case No. 1., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Public Law Board No. 2287. Conrail Case No. 2., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Public Law Board No. 2287. Conrail Case No. 3., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Public Law Board No. 2287. Conrail Case No. 4. Award No. 4. Claim Sustained., 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Public Law Board No. 2287. Conrail Case No. 5. Award No. 5. Claim Sustained., 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Public Law Board No. 2287. Conrail Case No. 6. Award No. 6. Claim Sustained., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Public Law Board No. 2388. South Buffalo Railway Co. No. 86. Sustained., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Public Law Board No. 2388. South Buffalo Railway Co. Special Board of Adjustment. Donald E Brunner., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1030-1173 (Box 19)
  - Special Board of Adjustment. RYA vs. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Special Board of Adjustment. RYA vs. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board. RYA vs. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Public Law Board Documents., 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Railroad Yardmasters. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Public Law Board No. 1836., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Public Law Board No. 1688. 1-3 5h. Penn Central., 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Public Law Board No. 1790. Awards No. 84,85,86,88. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Public Law Board No. 1830. Conrail., 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Public Law Board No. 1787. American Train Dispatchers Association. St. Louis-San Francisco., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Public Law Board No. 1830. Conrail. Diversion of Traffic. Court Proceedings., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Public Law Board No. 1876. Long Island Railroad., 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Public Law Board No. 1966. JJ Brown. No. GD-76811., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Public Law Board No. 1966. Neutral Preston Moore. Case Details., 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Public Law Board No. 1979. Erie Lackawanna Merger., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Public Law Board No. 1995. Seaboard Coast Line Railroad. Referee David Dolnick., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    November 28 1977.
  - Public Law Board No. 1995. Request for Interpretation. Seaboard Coast Line., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1177-1387 (Box 20)
  - US District Court. Judge Lynch., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    June 16 1976.
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 880. Conrail., 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Public Law Board No. 369. Third Party., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Public Law Board No. 520. Transportation Communications Employees Union and Penn Central Co., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Public Law Board No. 864. Baltimore and Ohio. Vacation Dispute. 1-3.3., 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Public Law Board No. 864. Baltimore and Ohio vs. RYA. Vacation Claims., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    March 30 1973.
  - Public Law Board No. 905. Nashville Terminal, Louisville and Nashville. 1-3.5(b)., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    June 8 1972.
  - Public Law Board No. 985. Dispute. Southern Railroad. Correspondence. 1-3.5, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Public Law Board No. 985. Southern Railway System. CA Lamb, Sr., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    October 2 and 3 1971
  - Public Law Board No. 1043. Central Georgie and the UTU. Third Party., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    July 17 1973.
  - Public Law Board No. 1291. Long Island Railroad. 1-3.5(d)., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    July 22 1974.
  - Public Law Board No. 1294. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac., 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    March 27 1978.
  - Public Law Board No. 1638. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad vs RYA., 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Public Law Board No. 1443. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. 1-3.5(f)., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    October 3 1975.
  - Public Law Board No. 1443. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad., 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Public Law Board No. 16557. Norfolk and Western Case No. 5., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Public Law Board No. 1657. Merger Protective Dispute. Norfolk and Western. Yardmaster Miscellaneous., 1975-1978 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Potomac Yard, Virginia. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co., 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Yardmaster Documents. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co., 1970-1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Public Law Board No. 1294. Potomac Yard Documents., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1299-1439 (Box 21)
  - Public Law Board No. 2419. Rock Island and RYA., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Public Law Board No. 2433. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Case No. 85. Section 6. TRIM., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Public Law Board No. 2441. Sick Pay., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Public Law Board No. 2486. Baltimore and Ohio., 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Public Law Board No. 2486. Case No. 2. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Haney., 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Public Law Board No. 2486. Case No. 3. Baltimore and Ohio. Porter., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Public Law Board No. 2486. Case No. 4. Baltimore and Ohio. Mallory. Award No. 2., 1978-1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Public Law Board No. 2538. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Crotty., 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Public Law Board No. 2562. Conrail. Buffalo., 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Hearing June 30 1980.
  - Public Law Board No. 2562. Conrail., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Public Law Board No. 2621. Conrail. Irvine., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Public Law Board No. 2637. Rock Island, Chicago North Western. Dolnick., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    April 10 1980.
  - Public Law Board No. 2660. Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Co., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western Case. BS Harnishfeqer., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    July 30 1981.
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Case No. 1. Norfolk and Western. RP Carter., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Case No. 2. Norfolk and Western. RP Carter., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Case No. 3 and 4. Norfolk and Western., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 5., 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Case No. 7. Norfolk and Western. RW Kahler., 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Case No. 8. Norfolk and Western. HE Lyons., 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 9. Anthony Homchik., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 10. FD Adams., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 11. SE Skeba., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 12. WA Wilder., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 13. EE Stover., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 14. FW Christopher., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 15. Frank J Christopher., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 16. TW Goodell., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 17. EJ Haver., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 18. MA Fantuz., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 19. James Bodo., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 20. E. Haver., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 21. DE Hensley., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 22. MP Schnabel., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 23. RG Riggle., 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 24. MO Corrado., 1973-1981 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 25. GP Smith., 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 26. Wingfield, Williams, Hancock, Gross., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 27. DA Ray, WA Wilder., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 31. TA Murray., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 28. WT Arnold., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 29. R Fillinger., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 30. R Yates., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 32. GP Smith., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Public Law Board No. 2719. Norfolk and Western. Case No. 33. JW Smart., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1440-1603 (Box 22)
  - Award No. 1030. Docket No. 1018. Baltimore and Ohio. M Grafton., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1032. Docket No. 1050. Southern Railroad. FL Baker., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1039. Docket No. 1032. TRRA. Blanket Vacation Claims., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1041. Docket No. 1034. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad. SD Brown., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1049. Docket No. 1049. Baltimore and Ohio. Warfield Claims., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1050. Docket No. 1039. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. QG Blackburn Claim., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1051. Docket No. 1043. Grand Trunk Western. Miller and Johnson., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1052. Docket No. 1045. Wabash Railroad. Claim., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 1054. Docket No. 1047. Chicago Northwestern. Claim., 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1056. Docket No. 1042. Grand Trunk Western. Maar Claims at Durand., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 1060. Docket No. 1053. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. JW Stinson Rest Day Claim., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 1068. Docket No. 1070. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad. Cass at Harlowton, Montana., 1954-1956 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1071. Docket No. 1073. Ogden Union Railroad and Depot. WB Daffron Disqualification., 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1072. Docket No. 1074. Grand Trunk Western. WH Skinner Disqualification., 1956 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1073. Docket No. 1075. The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co., 1954-1956 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1074. Docket No. 1076. Denver and Rio Grande Western. Joe Marzino Claim., 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1075. Docket No. 1078. Southern Railroad. Protest and Claims Account., 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1076. Docket No. 1046. TRRA. Request for Yardmaster Positions in St. Louis., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1078. Docket No. 1054. Houston Belt and Terminal Co. Carmical Case., 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1079. Docket No. 1059. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. JW Liesveld Claim., 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1080. Docket No. 1062. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific. Colby and Smith Claims., 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1082. Docket No. 1093. Missouri-Kansas-Texas. RS Brown Claims., 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1083. Docket No. 1079. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. WE Fipps Disqualification., 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1088. Docket No. 1084. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie., 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1606-1729 (Box 23)
  - Docket No. 252. Award No. 247. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. RS Miller., 1941-1945 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 247. Award No. 249. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. RE Lund., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 253. Award No. 253. Southern Railway Co., Chattanooga, Tennessee., 1943-1944 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 260. Award No. 263. Southern Pacific. FS Jones., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 271. Award No. 265. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Hubert Baker., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 264. Award No. 268. Pitcairn Yard., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 267. Award No. 270. West End Haselton Yard., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Docket No. 268. Award No. 271. Cherry Street Yard., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 269. Award No. 272. Lincoln Yard, Detroit., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 270. Award No. 267. JR Freidinger. Union Pacific., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 10)